Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
Can I leave?
Alps!
Let him go.
Why did you let him Osman Bey?
You should have let me tear him down and
give his bones to the dogs!
Umur Bey, I didn't want the son to
suffer from...
his father's mistakes.
Come to my tent.
I need to talk to you.
Aris the Lord.
Don't upset yourself.
You are going to be useful for the first
time in your life.
Take him out.
Umur Bey...
How can you, who is such a smart man,
fall into carelessness...
and send Malhun Hatun to Lord Nicola?
Don't you know we have hostiles?
I sent my daughter as a messenger to tell
him to hand Togay over us.
Umur Bey! How can you ignore us?
Are we talking about ignoring?
On which subject did you actually
consulted us?
And you say I am the one who
ignores you?
You made me do this Osman Bey.
If you had found that Togay dog...
I wouldn't have done this.
Umur Bey!
I told you to know your limits!
But you never listened to me.
This is my last warning.
Do not act before asking me ever again!
What is your decision, Osman Bey?
Tell me now.
I'll gather Beys.
Then I'll decide.
What happened to her?
Is she dead?
Ssshh! Stand up!
Stand up!
I'm talking to you!
There must be something wrong.
Go to the tent. Let our Bey know.
Deliver your swords to us.
We'll take you to the castle.
Throw your sword away.
Or I'll kill them.
I told you to throw it!
Take them!
- Quickly!
- Let go of me.
Let go of me.
We can't let the infidels take
Malhun Hatun away, Osman Bey.
I propose that we give the Lord,
take Malhun Hatun.
We need to meet Nicola andfind out
if Malhun Hatun alive or not...
Then, if we can find a way to take Malhun
Hatun back without giving the Lord away...
we shall attack.
Osman Bey, I'm afraid Nicola is going to
predict the same thing.
He'll want the Lord but he won't give
Malhun Hatun to us.
Swap is dangerous, Osman Bey.
We have to trick them.
Do you hear it Umur Bey?
I'll make a move to make
all these right.
What is your intention, Osman Bey?
What are you thinking of?
Umur Bey, you shall be our guest
a little more time.
Rest in your tent.
We are handling this.
Osman Bey, this is not the time to rest.
I'll come to the swap area, too.
You cannot object.
You have to obey, Umur Bey!
The daughter is mine,
the issue is mine
You can't do it without me!
You are going to see how we do it!
Your obligatory behaviour won't
bring peaceful friendship Osman Bey.
Be a friend to us.
Stay friendly.
The contrary won't work for you Umur Bey.
Alps!
Take Umur Bey to his tent.
Obviously, Nicola will try to trick us.
But I am going to trick him.
I'll go to the swap area
early with my alps, deploy there.
And Nicola won't know it.
And the other Alps will bring the Lord.
If Nicola tries something...
then I'll cut his head off in the field!
Let's go!
We shall hurry up!
What do you want?
You took too many lives, you shed blood.
That's what I heard.
I've brought you food.
Eat so that you can rouse yourself,
Malhun Hatun.
Only one of us is going to
get out of here!
You know that!
You are bad at predictions.
Eat.
Eat so that...
you can arrive at your tent.
What are you trying to say, Togay?
I'm not afraid of you, Togay!
Such a girl wouldn't be afraid, yes.
Your courage gives me power.
Malhun.
Burn in hell, Togay!
Burn in hell!
Hell, the place where Togay breathes in.
-What does this ignoble want Malhun Hatun?
-We'll see, Alaca.
We'll see.
You are worried.
What makes you, my Bey?
I am not worried.
I am angry, my Bala.
Are you angry because Malhun Hatun
is captured?
What is my purpose, Bala?
Tell me.
What is my purpose?
What have I been saying since
I conquered Kulucahisar.
- Inegol, you say.
- Yes.
I am talking about Inegol.
I'm talking about Bursa.
I'm talking about a state.
But...
What are my enemies doing?
They hamper you, my Osman.
Of course they do!
They are the enemy.
What about my friends?
They don't stand with you.
They are not with you.
- They retard the conquer.
- This is why I am angry!
This is why I'm eating my heart out, Bala!
However, however you...
you are not like them.
You stand with me like a mountain.
I always will, my Osman.
Always.
The Lord has been shot!
Protect the Lord!
Alps get in order!
Hold on Aris! Set a fire at once!
We'll brand the wound!
Come on!
Hold on Aris!
We can't let him die!
Hold on Aris! Hold on!
He will die.
Who did this Cerkutay, who?
An arrow which finds its target doesn't
only kill one, also sheds others' blood!
That kind of arrow this is.
What are we going to say to our Bey now?
May Allah save us from our Bey's wrath.
When we are sure we have Malhun Hatun,
we'll move with my sign.
This will be done today.
My Bey.
The Lord...
- Yes?
- They killed the Lord on the way.
My Bey, we were on the way...
Who did this Osman Bey?
Who, if not Nicola?
I'd say Togay but he is cooperating
with Nicola.
Nicola is coming my Bey.
Where is the Lord, Osman Bey?
They killed the Lord on the way.
Bring him!
Who did this?
If not you, who?
They are trying to set a game on us!
Give Malhun Hatun to me now!
We'll do whatever we do
in the battlefield.
Go to hell, Osman Bey!
Alps!
The captives...
are still mine.
Fall back now!
I'll make you pay for my Lord.
You'll hear about Malhun Hatun later.
What are we going to do, Osman Bey?
Let them go.
Soldier!
Everything goes alright, in sha Allah.
They take Malhun Hatun, give the Lord.
In sha Allah, my Bala.
In sha Allah.
Our alps shall come back safe and soud.
Then we are going to work on
the main point.
What is the main point, my Bala?
You tell me, Gonca. What are you thinking
about that makes you miss my words?
No way, my Bala.
I have been trying to chat here. You only
say in sha Allah.
We shall be done with it so
you start hearing again.
What is it, Bala?
What do you think it is, my Gonca?
I'm talking about the wedding.
Come on, Bala. This wasn't the only thing
I was thinking about.
I think it was, Gonca.
Don't worry. I'll remind Osman Bey
when he returns.
Whatever you say, my Bala.
You know the best.
Who did this?
Who?!
My dignity vanished while I was
trying to end Osman's.
Now all the Lord will doubt my power.
This is way better.
So much better.
The Lords will come under your security.
They'll run away from Osman's wrath.
You... you did it.
Who else could dare to do that?
Umur Bey couldn't protect the captive.
He couldn't save his daughter.
Umur Bey was shot in Osman's meeting.
Now his daughter is captived by us.
When you attack Sogut, Umur Bey won't
fight for Osman.
I know Umur Bey very well. He won't
fight for Osman Bey.
Without notifying me, do not...
Sir.
We have to talk.
The fat is in the fire. Think about the
opportunuties...
I've created for you, Nicola.
What is it Helen?
I have good news for you.
Where is my daughter, Osman Bey?
Did you get her?
The Lord was assassinated.
What?
He died.
What about my daughter?
She's in Nicola's hands.
You didn't take me there.
So I wouldn't act by myself,
huh Osman Bey?
Because it'd cost me dearly,
right Osman Bey?
Well this is the worst scenario Osman Bey!
Nicola will kill my daughter now that
the Lord is dead.
Nicola is not involved in this.
We have to know who is doing what
right now.
Osman Bey, this obligatory visit must end.
I must return to my tent.
We'll take care of ourselves from now on.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come.
Malhun Hatun will be in Nicola's
hunting ground.
Your visit will end.
But you cannot act by yourself.
Alps.
Untie her.
Where? Where?
Where are you taking her?
- Let go of her!
- Let go of me!
- My Hanım!
Can I come in my Bey?
Come brother.
Eyvallah (thank you) brother.
Get Alps ready, brother.
We have news from Inegol.
Nicola will take Malhun Hatun to
Ala Forest.
Why is he doing that, Osman Bey?
We'll see brother, we'll see.
He still suspects the spy in the castle.
So he didn't want to leave
Malhun Hatun alone.
He will take precautions on the way.
There will be lots of soldiers.
Don't worry, Osman Bey. Our Alps
pant for fight.
We'll set off at dawn. We'll take Malhun
Hatun and head back.
As you command, Osman Bey.
Eyvallah (thank you) brother.
Zulfikar was right. That woman called
Malhun must be inside.
Look, she is all silent.
She got what she deserved.
You love Malhun Hatun, right?
I'm fond of her. You?
She is totally a daughter of a Bey.
You are crazy.
Let's go back.
We have to notify Osman Bey.
Even if we take Malhun Hatun back, I'm
afraid she and her dad will cause trouble.
We've always been troubled since they
joined us, Osman Bey.
Togay was after Umur Bey, now us.
We are just getting started, brother. All
the problems of communities which...
we invited to join us
will be our problems, too.
They are just thinking of themselves.
It's not easy to manage all those
Beys and alps Osman Bey.
As long as Turkish tents don't unite...
There will always be Mongols, Byzantines
and others on our lands.
- Zülfükar's was right.
- Eyvallah.
Guardians are keeping watch, my Bey.
Malhun Hatun is inside.
- How many are there?
- Four, my Bey.
Two more must be there. According to the
horseshoe tracks, they are six or seven.
Now listen to me carefully.
Be careful.
Malhun Hatun.
Zülfikar.
My valiant.
Come on.
They are getting closer.
Inna Lillahi wa inna ilayhi raji'un
"Verily we belong to Allah,
and verily to Him do we return."
My Bey! We got ambushed!
They are getting closer.
Now, Alps!
Come on Alps!
Osman Bey.
Osman Bey, zülfikar's news was a bait.
They martyred Zülfikar.
Take his body to his Sheik.
Oh, Flatyos.
I am sorry you couldn't see that.
I'll take revenge for your father.
I'll shave Turks off Bıtinya like I
shave my haris off!
Good job.
We'll break the whole Kayı with
one shot today.
Let's see what Osman does when
he sees the papa.
If Kolonoz had come, I'd have sent more
soldiers.
I knew you were provoking your soldiers
against me because I didn't go to church.
But I didn't know you were serving Osman.
You told him how you could let Malhun
Hatun escape from the castle.
Smart move.
You know every secret of ours.
You are too smart for a papa. Did Osman
buy you by gold?
His name is Zülfikar.
He was the student of edebalı.
Whoa, whoa.
A faithful dervish.
What else does Osman know?
Whatever he needs to know to take your
castle and cut your head off your body!
"I bear witness that there is no god
but Allah, and...
I bear witness that Muhammad
is the Messenger of Allah."
Let's see if the latest news he gave
to Osman will end Osman or not.
Zülfikar!
Are you here to celebrate our victory,
Togay?
When Gokboru dives in a jackals, he fights
with his paws so that his teeth stay clear.
What doesd this mean?
Osman killed the soldiers with his paws.
None left alive.
How can this be?
How can you know that?
A wounded soldier died in my hands while
coming here to tell you.
Damn it.
Osman.
Gokboru gains power from his faith,
not his herd.
His faith becomes his herd's faith.
If you don't ruin his faith,
he'll ruin you.
He will, and not by ruining just you.
Damn it.
I'll destroy Sogut!
This would end you, Nicola. I advise you
to realise the treasure you have.
- What treasure Togay?
- Malhun Hatun.
Let Malhun Hatun open the doors
of Sogut for you.
How?
In the slightest mistake we make, he'll
kill my daughter.
The moment he sees alps in front of his
castle, we lose Malhun.
What are we going to do then, my Bey?
We'll pay him.
We'll pay Nicola to let Malhun free.
He'll want everything we have, my Bey.
Bahadır! My everything is in that
infidel's hands.
We can recover the property.
But she is my only daughter.
Of coursemy Bey.
- Can I come in my Bey?
- Come.
Alaca Hatun! Where is my daughter?
They let us free, but kept her, my Bey.
What do they want?
- Lord Nicola wants to see you my Bey.
- What is that about?
He wants a secret meeting that nobody
hears. He said he'd let Malhun Hatun free.
He will let her free, ha?
My Bey! This may be a bait.
They may want to capture you as well.
We can't reject this opportunity.
As he said, I'll meet alone.
We'll set off at dawn tomorrow.
Take alps and come with me.
As you command, my Bey.
Are you now stealing hatuns' water,
Cerkutay?
I need hot water?
Why do you need hot water?
- Alps doesn't question.
- Cerkutay.
As Dervish Yunus said, people need to move
forward, so we will.
They won't realise.
As they martyr us, we'll reborn.
They will think we are decreased.
- I asked where you are taking it to!
- I won't tell you, you mad girl!
What are you fighting for again, you two?
- What is that water for?
- I won'T speak.
Cerkutay, tell us.
What is that for?
For Wudu .
Is that right?
Do alps use hot water for Wudu?
Answer him, Cerkutay.
It's not for me.
So, for whom?
So you take so much care of
Ghazi Bamsı Bey.
What about you?
Why don't you take care of yourself?
Hey, you valiant whose heart is muslim.
Why are you still not saying shahada?
I'm a cruel.
I killed so many.
I killed women.
I killed children.
I was cruel.
I was cruel to the sinless.
I am a cruel.
Oy, oy, oy, oy.
Son.
Being muslim is so hard.
I'd feel shy against Mohammad.
I am afraid of his Allah.
Can you be afraid of someone you love?
Just repent.
Repent turns poison into honey.
It turns thorn into rose.
Even cruels can enter.
We have diwan for the comer, we have
water for the ones who take a Wudu.
I'll come.
Where is my daughter?
Soldier!
Get out!
Aren't you sick of all these like me,
Umur Bey?
What are you after Nicola?
- I'm after your friendship.
- So why did you cooperate with Togay?
Why did you capture my daughter?
What should I have done? Should I have
faced Black Shaman Togay and Geyhatu...
and run away from my lands?
Don't Umur bey!
Do not.
Do not let my trust for you down.
I am hosting you alone and unarmed
in my place.
We both know...
Neither you nor me can resist to
Geyhatu's power.
I don't care about your daughter at all.
Umur Bey, the only thing I wanted was my
Lord who Osman kidnapped.
But Osman couldn't even bring him to me
safe and sound.
He couldn't protect you jus tlike he
couldn't protect my Lord.
As for me, my intention is to
trade with Turks.
That decent Beys like you be at my border
isn't only safe for me...
but it is also safe for my empire.
I feel safe when Geyhatu is busy with you.
Umur Bey, you are a Turk Bey
who is a honorable...
You are a Bey who challanged Geyhatu.
But in the end, you ended
up at my borders.
That I have Beys like you at my border
keep me away from Mongols and trouble.
And by the way, I worked with Togay
because of you.
- What about Osman?
- Osman.
Osman is young. He is a dasher.
He wants the treasure in my land.
But both you and me know that the biggest
treasure is trading.
I think an experienced Bey like you can
take charge of Osman...
whose head is in the clouds, Umur Bey.
I prefer you kill me and my daughter right
here right now...
instead of betraying Osman Bey.
Umur Bey, oh Umur Bey.
What I want from you is not betrayal.
I want you to be a big brother to Osman.
You should show him the way...
keep him out of trouble.
How?
How can I do that?
What are you thinking of?
Umur Bey, I'll give you an opportunity to
enhance our friendship and...
we'll make trade.
I need four hundred horses.
For you to give them to your soldiers
in war?
For you to trample Kayı Tent down with
their hooves?
No no no. In order to resist to Geyhatu
When he comes here,
Umur Bey, Turks are not a threat for me.
Mongols are.
While we are fighting each other with
Osman here, Geyhatu already got Ilhanlı.
Sooner or later he's going to come here.
I want to have power to resist...
when the trouble knocks on my door.
You'll give me horses.
I'll open the trade door of...
Iznık, Bursa, Constantinople, Umur Bey.
Furthermore, you'll not pay fees.
And so, with the gold you gain, you can
control Osman...
who is acting like a brutal horse.
You are offering me trade routes in return
of keeping Osman down, right?
Umur Bey, I want to live in peace, gain
strenght with the help of your friendship...
What if I run off with Malhun and
never give you those horses?
I know you are such a red-blooded Bey
who won't betray Osman.
Just like I know you are a honorable Bey
who won't live in the shadow of Osman.
Decision is yours, Umur Bey.
Those soldiers who will ride the horses,
who will fight against the Mongols should...
be able to ride a horse as well as
a Turk.
What is your offer?
- Father.
- Daughter.
Umur Bey.
What is your offer?
There are stable boys who can educate
the horses I'll send you.
To educate your soldiers against
our common enemies.
Smartly.
Smartly said.
I kept my word.
I gave you your daughter safe and sound.
Now it's your turn.
I'll think about it...
and notify you soon.
Dear Helen, see our guests off.
May your path be open.
This way.
Father, what horses is this ignobl
talking about?
I'll tell you once we arrive in the tent.
You are the biggest fraud I have ever seen
Nikola.
You will raise warrior cavalries from
Kalanoz's soldiers.
Against Lord of the Lords Geyhatu.
With them, I will not only take Söğüt
but also Bitinya.
I will exterminate Geyhatu's enemies
in this land.
Of course, with your help, Togay.
He was a valiant dervish.
He accepted the hardest mission.
He got into the infidel's heart and
became our eyes and ears.
Allah...
... may forgive him.
Rest in peace.
-Amin.
We lost another valiant.
Then we will take another valiant's
revenge.
We will.
We will take his revenge.
We will all stand up for the cause
they died for.
As our martyrs march to heaven,
we will draw our swords for victory.
Inform the Turkmen tribes.
Say Osman Bey is opening his flag.
All the Beys shall gather soldiers for
our army.
What about Malhun Hatun, Osman Bey?
I will set up this game to get her back.
It is broken by the martyrdom of Zülfikar.
What about Umur Bey? He is gone.
He wants to act alone.
I know, Emmi.
I know.
But I already set up my new plan.
Nikola will think that we are desperate.
He can think so.
We'll say we'll ransom to get her.
He will suspect at first but...
... he will accept it later on.
We will both get Malhun Hatun and finish
our business with Nikola.
However, Umur Bey is also considering
paying the ransom.
He will want to negotiate with Nikola
this time.
First, we must stop Umur Bey.
Let's not lose any time.
May Allah be with us.
-Amin.
Thankfully, this is over.
But I was so worried that infidel was to
break his word.
What should we think, Father?
Did he scruple to kill me?
Of course, he did.
He is aware of our power.
Obviously, he investigated us well and
what he found out scared him.
He chose to benefit by trading rather than
fighting Kızılbeyoğlu and get ruined.
He is a two tongue snake. If one says
peace the other says warç
You are worried Nikola is playing and
trapping your father right?
Thinking that Togay is with him.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey, Osman Bey and Bala Hatun
are here.
Let them in.
Umur Bey.
Osman Bey, Bala Hatun.
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Malhun Hatun.
So you are back.
Welcome back.
How could that infidel let you go?
Isn't there enough trouble for him,
Osman Bey?
Thanks to you...
... he couldn't consider going against us.
They killed my Zülfikay...
... my valiant dervish.
I paid hard for this.
I'm sorry for your loss, Osman Bey.
I hope his place is heaven.
Thank you.
Thank you, but...
...the murder of the man sent for
barter...
... the unexpected release of Malhun Hatun
...
... shows that this is a vile game.
Doesn't it, Umur Bey?
I came to check on the women of tribe,
if they have any trouble.
You thought well, Bala Hatun.
My absence was their only problem.
Since I am back, there is no problem.
Being in the dungeons when you should have
been with your women caused us trouble.
Since you are back, we can rest now.
Maşallah, Maşallah.
You must have missed each other.
We have things to do.
Thank you for coming.
Sure, Umur Bey.
What is that you can not say with your
sweet mouth, my Bala?
I know, like me, you don't believe
Umur Bey either, my Bey.
Nikola wants to get along with him by
giving him his daughter.
He wants to set us against each other,
with Umur Bey.
What about you?
What will you say, my Bey?
I will watch them, my Bala.
I will watch them.
Boran and Gonca Hatun are waiting.
If we look for a day without trouble,
we will not find a day to feast.
Are you saying it, my Osman?
Shall the wedding feast begin?
It shall begin.
Boran, come here.
Come here.
Yes, my Bey.
Why are you keeping Gonca Hatun await?
Marry her if you will.
My Bey.
It seems you don't have any
preparation.
Then, let's arrange a feast at Söğüt.
Set a huge table. Everyone will join.
Also, those in need will be happy.
- What do you think, my Bala?
- That's nice, my Osman.
- Your command, my Bey.
- Yes, I command.
Come on.
Start the preparations.
Alps!
Come on.
We're leaving.
Nikola wants 400 horses from us.
However, we only have 100 horses to sell.
We should go to Söğüt and
see the merchants.
It will be possible if we
have their horses too.
Will we sell horses to non-Muslims
so that they can attack Turks?
You will lead them when
the caravan enters İnegöl.
The grooms will go İnegöl with the horses.
Nikola may think of attacking Turks
with the Turk horses.
I think of something too.
Bahadır says those walls
can't be surpassed.
- Then we will open the door inside.
- Yes.
And we will send our Alps.
We will take the castle
that Osman Bey wants to take.
Alaca Hatun!
Yes, my Bey.
Prepare us a dining table.
I will eat with my daughter.
It will look good on you, my Gonca.
I wish Selcan Mother was here.
Selcan Mother couldn't come but...
she may come to Aygül's wedding.
Who says that I will have
a wedding, Bala Hatun?
You can't guess.
A man may seem good to you.
He wouldn't dare.
Come on, Hatuns!
Work.
We have a wedding.
It is Nikola's and Togay's trick.
What they want to do is to face off
Osman against Umur Bey.
- Then who killed the Lord?
- Togay.
He wants to deal with Nikola in return
for Umur Bey and Osman.
- Malhun Hatun is coming.
- Togay...
- He did it again.
- She shouldn't know I'm here.
- May it be easy.
- Thank you, my Hanım.
- Welcome.
They say you are the strongest
merchants around.
Thanks to them.
Merchant Abdullah bin Melik.
What do you need? There's
nothing we can't supply.
I want 100 horses.
Quick.
Can I ask you why?
We will have a trade
in İnegöl Castle.
When will you give me the horses?
However...
selling horses to Osman Bey's enemy...
will endanger not only you but also us.
It can't happen.
Aren't you a merchant?
Do your job.
The rest is my responsibility.
I'm sorry.
However, we don't sell animals.
We don't do that kind of stuff. However,
what we spoke will stay between us.
It's a secret.
Have a good journey, my Hanım.
Wow, wow.
Nikola dealt with them obviously.
If we gave horses to her, Osman
would kill us.
Let's see what it leads to.
We know what it leads to.
Osman Bey and Umur Bey will fight.
- May it be easy.
- Thank you, my Bey. Welcome.
- Welcome, my Bey.
- Welcome to our bazaar, my Bey.
- May it be easy.
- Welcome, my Bey.
Welcome, my Bey.
Thank you.
- Welcome, my Bey.
- Have a good work.
Welcome, my Bey.
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
- May it be easy.
- Thank you, my Bey.
Mashallah, it tastes the same.
- I always have the best one, my Bey.
- Thank you.
- May it be easy.
- Thank you, my Bey.
Uncle.
What happened?
We have news from
Malhun Hatun, Osman Bey.
What is it?
We know why Nikola left Malhun Hatun free.
Nikola and Umur Bey made
a trade agreement.
Umur Bey will sell horses to Nikola.
His daughter Malhun is looking
for 100 horses.
What are you saying, uncle?
Horses are the swords.
You can't give them to the enemy.
I did everything I could so that they
couldn't supply what they need.
Don't worry.
Thank you, uncle.
Malhun Hatun!
Yes, Osman Bey.
Did I give you things so that
you could be my enemy?
What are you talking about, Osman Bey?
Isn't Nikola my enemy?
Am I not fighting with him?
You being friends with him means you
are my enemy.
Tell me what you want to say, Osman Bey.
How can you sell horses to my enemy while
it is up to me that you do a trade?
- How did you hear about that?
- Answer my question.
Our tent needs that trade.
Why is it wrong?
You are selling horses to my
enemy, so that...
he can kill my Alps easily and...
he can attack Muslims!
Bayhoca's blood is still fresh.
Now go and tell your father...
I don't have consent for this.
And tell him...
he should be afraid of my wrath!
Come on!
Baysungur.
My Bey.
They won't stop.
Follow them.
Your command, my Bey.
Osman Bey's last words mean a
threat to us.
What will we do?
He is afraid of falling from grace.
He doesn't want us to be powerful.
If he finds out we will send
our men to İnegöl Castle...
while he is trying to gather some
Beys to do the same...
Osman Bey will prevent us
from finding horses.
Then we will give the horses we can find.
The caravan will be on the road today.
Kalanoz.
He will be in my castle
with his army three days later.
Before your army comes, Osman
shouldn't be seen.
Only me and you know that
Kalanoz is coming.
I scratched Osman's men's
eyes in the castle.
He can't get any information.
I will equip
the cavalry coming with Kalanoz.
It will make me more powerful.
If you don't play trick behind me.
I won't. Don't worry.
Only if you give me some of your
soldiers to command me.
- I will make your work easier.
- How?
Osman's aide, Boran Alp, will marry soon.
They won't have a wedding night.
I will destroy Osman's belief in Allah...
and destroy his army's trust in him.
The new bride's blood will
paint Osman's tent red.
While Osman's tent is in the
grief of the new bride...
you will go to Söğüt.
You thought I couldn't see
your wedding feast, huh?
Thank Allah, Göktuğ.
Inshallah, we can see yours too.
For our Zülfikar brother...
Al-Fatihah.
May Allah let Zülfikar brother
go to heaven.
Amin.
We are all sad.
Hewever...
our Efendi, our Prophet...
commanded us to marry
and to have children.
He said he will be proud
of our abundance...
on the day of judgment.
For this reason, we
will marry and we will have children.
The Kayı Tent will be bigger.
It will make its people feel safe...
and its enemies fear.
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
You gave us honor, my Sheikh.
I'm glad you're here, my Sheikh.
Thank you, my daughter.
My Sheikh.
Mashallah, my daughter Gonca.
Mashallah, my Boran Alp.
May Allah grant you happiness..
and with better intentions.
Amin.
Stay together when you are
happy or in pain.
Inshallah.
Raise your children for Kayı and Islam.
- Inshallah.
- Inshallah, my Sheikh.
My brother, Boran Alp is very excited.
We were the same as him, brother.
They are finally together.
Abdurrahman Ghazi...
We are old now, huh?
Yes, brother.
May Allah grant us to leave
this life with Shahada.
Inshallah, my Ghazi.
Inshallah.
Amin.
What, mad woman? Why
are standing alone?
Why aren't you with the Alps?
Göktuğ is with Boran.
Bamsı Bey is with Abdurrahman Ghazi.
- I...
- You...
I wanted someone mad like me.
- Stop it.
- Stop what?
Stop saying these words.
I told you, my Bey.
A warrior's lover is his sword.
This is the hardest of all wars, Cerkutay.
This is the hardest of all wars.
Don't worry, father.
We will go safe and sound, Inshallah.
We don't know those lands.
Be careful.
Bahadır!
Take care of my daughter.
Okay, my Bey.
If Nikola asks why the horses lack...
I will tell him we will get
more with the grooms as soon as possible.
Okay.
Tell the grooms what they will do there.
They will be our eyes and
ears in İnegöl Castle.
Come on.
Have a good journey.
May Allah help you.
Thank you.
My Bey.
Umur Bey's caravan is going to İnegöl.
She didn't listen to me.
- What happened, Osman Bey?
- Umur Bey...
Umur Bey takes horses to İnegöl.
- You say so?
- Nikola won't get those horses.
Boran. Stay here with my
brother and uncle.
Don't leave the feast alone.
We don't know what
unbelievers are capable of.
- Hatuns! Go to the tent.
- Your command, my Bey.
Come on, Alps!
The wind is with me.
The arrow...
is with the death!
Alps!
Battle order!
Protect Hatuns!
Boran.
Be careful!
Mother!
Come on!
- Come on.
- Allah is eternal!
Come on, valiants!
The arrow...
is with the death.
Gonca!
Togay.
Boran!
- Abdurrahman Ghazi!
Abdurrahman Ghazi!
- My Ghazi!
Hold on, my Ghazi!
Don't leave me, my Ghazi.
Hold on.
I think my time is over, brother.
Don't say that.
My Gonca!
Abdurrahman Ghazi...
Don't leave me alone, my Ghazi.
Allah heard our prayers, brother.
"I bear witness that there
is no deity but Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammad
is the messenger of Allah."
Togay!
Abdurrahman Ghazi...
My Gonca.
You will be okay.
- Do you have something to say, Osman Bey?
- I already said what I have to say.
The swords speak when
words are not enough.
Alps!
Take the caravan!
Don't feel pity for anyone if
they make any move.
Come on!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com